■
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：亲爱的小饭  冰蓝  威廉  丁小七  王大可
时间轴：浓子   校对：olivia_xuxu   后期&总监：瓜瓜
摩  登
家  庭
第六季 第一集
我来给你擦  老公
Let me get that, husband.
在经历了状况频出的婚礼
After a storybook wedding
和梦幻的蜜月之后
and a magical honeymoon,
米奇尔和我终于喜结连理
Mitchell and I are finally newlyweds.
你不觉得坐在你自己的椅子上
Are you sure you wouldn't be more comfortable
更舒服一点吗
in your own chair?
别再说什么"你的""我的"了
There's no more "My chair" Or "Your chair."
几星期前  我们度完蜜月回来
So we got back from our honeymoon several weeks ago,
感觉就像还未...
and it feels like it never --
还未结束吗  老天呐
Never ended? Oh, my gosh.
感觉我们同心同德
It's like we have one mind and one heart.
还同椅
And one chair.
结婚三周月纪念日快乐
Happy three-month anniversary.
是今天吗
Oh, is that today?
我们公司今天有个无聊的鸡尾酒会
So, listen, I have this boring cocktail thing at the office,
但我应该六点就能到家了
but I should be home by 6:00,
然后我们可以直接去参加派对
and then we can head to the party.
给你的  小爸  大爸送的  又来了
For you, dad. From dad. Again.
花吗  但你昨天刚送花给我了呀
Flowers? But you just got me flowers yesterday.
你昨天早餐也吃了麦片啊
Well, you also had cereal yesterday.
我不介意今天可以再吃一点
And I wouldn't mind having some today.
怀念以前家里没这么多蜜蜂的时候
Sure was nice when this house wasn't full of bees.
女士要再来点糖浆吗
More syrup for milady?
何乐而不为  谢谢  您真好
Why, thank you, kind sir.
克莱尔  你和卢克做的曲奇饼还有吗
Claire, do we still have any of those cookies that you and Luke baked?
我们是那种拿曲奇饼当早餐的家庭吗
Are we the kind of family that has cookies for breakfast?
当然  我们就是
Yes, we are!
好耶  好耶
Yeah! Yeah!
有蝴蝶
A butterfly!
天呐
Oh, my god!
我们度过了
We are having...
有史以来最完美的
...the most perfect summer...
夏天
...ever.
别误会
Don't get me wrong,
邓菲家的生活还是很欢乐的
the Dunphys have had some great days.
只是这种时光总是断断续续的
We just have a little trouble stringing them together.
我们的最好纪录是连续八天的幸福日子
Our record was eight consecutive blissful days --
那是在2007年12月
December 2007.
简直是我们的光明节
It was our Hanukkah.
这个夏天  邓菲家所有人都相处融洽
This summer, all the Dunphys are just clicking.
没错  海莉和卢克和睦相处
Yeah, Haley and Luke are getting along,
艾丽克斯去给穷人盖房子了
Alex is off building houses for the poor.
我知道那听起来挺可怕的  但是她喜欢
Which I know sounds awful, but she loves it.
我的时尚博客人气暴涨
My fashion blog is blowing up.
我搞起了视频聊天秀
I started doing these live video chats,
现在我的频道有五万多订阅者
and now I have over 50,000 subscribers!
而且  我的头发状态好极了
Oh, plus, my hair has never looked better.
我不信教
I'm not a religious person...
但我就是幡然醒悟了
but I just woke up.
菲尔搞起了园艺
Phil has been gardening.
而我也有时间跟朋友小聚  读读名著
I've had time to catch up and read the classics.
那是在她不需要帮我完成
...when she isn't busy helping me
我的魔镜消失魔术的时候
with my magic-mirror disappearing trick.
我刚要说  突然之间  我爱上了魔术
I'm just gonna say it -- suddenly, I love magic.
我才不管现在是不是中午
I don't care if it's the middle of the day.
我只想把你关进箱子
I just want to put you in a box
往你身上插"剑"
and stick swords in you.
让这个夏天更加梦幻的是
If this summer wasn't magical enough,
我都还没吃到过一个坏李子
I haven't had a single bad plum!
天呐
Oh, my god!
这个拉链呢
So, the zipper --
天呐
oh, my god!
Oh, my god!
曼尼
Manny!
来  跟你的兄弟姐妹们聊聊
Come! Talk to your cousins!
你们好
Hola!
曼尼  你为什么把他们冻起来
Manny, why you freeze the Colombians?
如果我跟其中一个聊起来
If I talk to one of them,
我就得跟其他50个聊
I have to talk to 50 of them.
就当作是生日礼物啊
Just do it as a birthday gift.
你总是这样
You always do this.
你的生日在下个星期呢
Your birthday's not till next week.
不是我的生日
Not mine.
今天是你萝莎丽奥婶婶82岁生日
It's aunt Rosario's 82nd birthday today.
所以那些山羊才都戴着派对帽
That's why all the goats are wearing the party hats.
你看
Look!
曼尼
Manny!
大家好
Hi, everyone.
新眼镜是不是又漂亮又时髦
Pretty snazzy new cheaters, huh?
才五块钱
Five bucks.
很值  对吧
I know, right?!
我老公年纪是比较大
My husband is an older man,
但他还不是老头子
but he's not an old man.
但穿上运动服  现在又戴上老花镜
But with the track suit and -- and now the glasses,
他最近好像不再努力打扮了
it's like he just stopped trying lately.
生活不能只求舒适啊
Comfort is not everything.
成人礼后  我的脚趾就再没知觉了
My toes have been numb since my quinceanera.
我们五点再去酒吧
We don't have to be at drinks till 5:00,
我要去办点事
so I'm gonna run a few errands,
戴眼镜去兜兜风
take these bad boys for a spin.
杰  你为什么不穿我给你买的新衣服
Ay, Jay, why don't you wear that new outfit that I just got you?
那条多余的拉链显得太花哨了
Uh, a little flashy, that extra zipper.
就像一部没有目的地的楼梯
Like a staircase to nowhere.
是啊  但会让你看起非常
Yeah, but it makes you look very --
亲爱的  我很抱歉  掉在你脚趾上了
Honey, I'm so sorry. Right on your toes.
没关系  你可以把公用电话砸我脚上
It's fine. You can drop a pay phone on my foot.
我一点感觉也没有
I don't feel a thing anymore.
现在  我可爱的助手来协助我了
And now, as my lovely assistant joins me,
我要开始念咒语了
it's time to chant the incantation
将这位美女送到第六次元
that will send this fair maiden into the sixth dimension.
借梅林的帽子  格拉曼思雅的女巫之名
By the hat of Merlin, by the witches of Gramanthia,
我们为您奉上精彩的表演  消失
we do make this offering to you -- be gone!
成功了吗  我消失了吗
Did I do it? Did I disappear?
差一点  露出了点头
Almost. Just a little bit of forehead.
我可以再蹲低点
Oh, I can scrunch down.
这就是热爱
There's love.
你们好啊
Hey, guys.
太贴心了  你把筛粉机带来了
Sweet! You brought the sifter.
我可以做大黄派了
Now I can start my rhubarb pie.
我能帮你摘大黄吗
Ooh, can I help pick the rhubarb?
带路吧  小猫咪
Lead the way, kitten.
有人要吃李子吗
Anybody want a plum?
不用了
I'm good.
我给你拿瓶无醇啤酒
I'll grab you a roadie.
这么问可能不太合适
There is no easy way to ask this,
但你们这是嗑药了吗
but are you all high?
才不是  米奇尔  我们很幸福
No, Mitchell. We're happy.
我正在努力逃离幸福
Oh, I'm trying to get away from "Happy."
好吧  用最简洁的方法
All right, in the briefest possible way,
你直接告诉我是怎么回事吧
why don't you let me know what's going on?
小卡拒绝结束蜜月
Okay, Cam refuses to let the honeymoon end.
我收到了无数的花  和肉麻短信
I have a house full of flowers, endless romantic texts.
我知道  我听起来像个不懂感恩的混蛋
I know, I know, I sound like an ungrateful jerk.
是的
You do.
累死人了
It's exhausting.
更别提我完全无法给他对等的爱
Not to mention impossible to reciprocate.
天呐
Oh, my god!
总之
Um, anyway,
你觉得我该不该跟他温柔地说下
do you think that maybe I should talk to him gently
让他适可而止
about taking it down a notch?
绝对不行  下场会很惨烈
No, absolutely not. That never ends well.
显然你看成了"刻薄点"
Clearly you thought this said "Be mean."
[你是我的]
-菲尔  亲爱的  -不
- Phil, honey, no. - No.
好吧  别担心  我...
It's -- okay, don't worry, I...
那都不是情人节呢
And it wasn't even Valentine's Day.
所以你的建议是按兵不动
So your advice is to do nothing.
是的  米奇尔  虽然这听起来很可怕
Yes, Mitchell, as horrible as this sounds,
但你得忍气吞声  让自己被他宠爱
you need to suck it up and let yourself be loved,
小卡最后会降低浪漫程度的
and Cam will end up dialing back the romance.
你可能还会怀念过去呢
You might just miss it.
我就是
I know I do.
好了  给我的小蜜桃一个李子
Here we are. A plum for my peach.
是吗
Do you?
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
他没事吧
Is he okay?
他是米奇尔
He's Mitchell.
我甚至都不想聊那事
Look, I didn't even want to talk about it.
咱家现在顺风顺水的
We've had such a great thing going on here.
我可不想让那种负能量进屋
I don't want to let that kind of negativity in the house.
艾丽克斯
Alex!
我们以为你下周才回来呢
We didn't think you were coming back until next week.
我提前回来了
I got a ride home early.
这简直是最烂的夏天
This has been the worst summer ever!
当心点  你个蠢货
Careful, you idiot!
你才是蠢货
You're an idiot!
昨晚我的帐篷坏了
And last night, my tent ripped,
所以我不得不
so I had to sleep
靠着一辆面包车睡在一块胶合板下面
under a plywood board leaning up against a van.
递我一张纸巾吧
Pass me a napkin.
夫人的胳膊断了吗
Is milady's arm broken?
你的胳膊就要被我打断了
Yours is about to be.
祖国珍贵的花朵
Aww, precious flowers.
反正老鼠那么多  我也睡不着
Not that I could sleep with all the rats.
顺便说一句
And, by the way,
如果你们开始咳血  那是我的错
if any of you start coughing up blood, my bad.
我觉得我带回了瘟疫
I think I brought back the plague.
我在干嘛呢
What am I doing?
我把书包忘在车道了
I think I left my backpack in the driveway.
别踢我
Stop kicking me!
是你在踢我
You're kicking me!
对不起  我今天有些烦躁
I'm sorry. I'm just fidgety today.
没关系
It's okay.
吃块曲奇饼会有帮助
A cookie might help.
这是你想要的纸巾
Here's that napkin you wanted.
我拿了信
I got the mail!
给我一张
Would it have killed you
没沾番茄酱的纸巾你会死吗
to give me one without ketchup on it?
走开
Move!
你那边够宽敞了
You have room!
不  搬走  你都40岁了
No, move out! You're 40!
好了  够了
Okay. That's enough.
卢克  你去给花园浇水吧
Luke, why don't you go water our garden.
海莉  消失一会儿吧
Haley, just disappear for a minute.
反正你也帮不上忙
Well, it's not like you could help with that.
说到人家痛处了
Abracad-ouch.
艾丽克斯回家了真好  对吧
Well, it's great having Alex home, huh?
太棒了
So great.
你不会觉得是她让我们...
You don't think that she's the reason why we --
不  我不觉得
No. No, I do not.
我们都知道这个迷人的夏天
We both knew that this charmed summer
迟早会遭遇不顺
had to have a bump in it somewhere.
是啊
Yes. Yeah.
艾丽克斯回家
And it's not like Alex coming home
又不会让我们的快乐咒语顿时失效
could suddenly throw off our whole happy mojo.
那李子好吃吗
How's that plum?
挺好吃的  天呐
Great. Oh, my god.
-她来了  -她来了
- There she is! - There she is!
你回家真是太好了  亲爱的
Oh, so happy to have you home, honey.
天呐  是只蝙蝠
Oh, my god! It's a bat!
怎么回事
What's happening?!
把它弄出去
Get it out of house!
弄出去
Get it away!
难以置信
This is unbelievable.
干洗工又搞丢了我的一件衬衣
The dry cleaner lost another one of my shirts.
你知道那件好看的
You know that nice,
红白蓝相间的夏威夷衬衣吧
red-white-and-blue Hawaiian one?
是啊  那件真的不错
Yes, that was a very nice one.
这是他搞丢的第四件夏威夷衬衣了
That's the fourth Hawaiian shirt he's lost.
我告诉你
I'm telling you,
这事要发展成罪案新闻报头条了
this is a "Dateline" story waiting to happen.
跟你们大家聊天很开心
Great talking with you all,
但有人想打个招呼
hey, but someone wants to say hi.
不要
No, no!
杰
Jay!
大家好
Hi, guys.
还是不会说西语
Nope, still don't speak Spanish.
但是看到你们还是好高兴啊
Always so much fun seeing you guys, though.
听着  我...
Listen, I --
-歌洛莉亚  -怎么
- Gloria? - Hmm?
你表弟穿着我的那件
Your cousin's wearing
黑黄桃色相间的夏威夷衬衣
my black, yellow, and peach Hawaiian shirt.
拜托  杰
Ay, please, Jay!
好像全世界
Like you're the only man
就你有那件衬衣一样
in this whole wide world that owns that shirt.
这种独特的设计不仅会
These designer specs don't
让我的眼睛显得很明亮
just make my eyes pop.
我还能看见左边口袋上被雪茄烫的印迹
I can see the cigar burn I put on the left pocket.
这是个巧合
It's a coincidence.
还有很多衣服呢
There's a lot of those.
比如说你叔叔的帽衫
Like according to your uncle's hoodie here,
他穿的是我在布坎南高中的田径队队服
he was on my track team at Buchanan High.
各位  这样吧
Hey, guys. Tell you what.
不如我们换换口味  尝尝美国食物
Why don't we sample some American food for a change?
你把我的衣服寄去了哥伦比亚吗
So, you're sending my clothes to Colombia?
只是旧衣服啦
Just the old ones, and --
他们寄回来了大部分衣服
and they send most of them back.
原来如此
And there it is.
你对我的穿衣风格有意见吗
Do you have a problem with the way I dress?
杰  我非常爱你
Jay, I love you very, very much.
我也非常爱你  但我问的不是这个
And I love you very much, but that wasn't the question.
只是有时候我觉得
It's just that sometimes I feel like
你可以在穿着打扮上做出更大的努力
you could make a bigger effort on your appearance.
你终于说了
And there it is.
别再这么说了
Please stop saying that.
我最近就是觉得
It's just that I feel that lately
你不再用心为我打扮自己了
you don't make an effort to look good for me,
但我从来都为你精心装扮自己的
and I'm always making an effort to look my best for you.
为我吗  是嘛
For me? Sure.
怎么了
What?
我们直说吧  你不是在为我装扮自己
Well, let's face it, you don't really doll up for me --
你是为了自己
you do it for you.
你做头发  做指甲
You get your hair done, you get your nails done.
所以我不打扮自己你也没问题吗
Oh, so you wouldn't mind if I stopped fixing myself up?
没问题  因为我爱的是你
No, because I love you for you.
既然我们要说实话
And since we're being honest,
其实我有时认为
I actually think sometimes...
你有点打扮过度了
you overdo it.
你终于说了
And there it is.
这句话不是这么用的
You're using it wrong.
不  这很好
No, this is good.
知道你一点也不在乎非常好
It's good to know that -- that you don't care.
我以后可以节省很多时间了
This is gonna save me so much time in the future.
很好
Good.
Good!
曼尼
Manny!
为什么
Why?
我不管俗不俗气
I don't care if it's cliché?
我就是很喜欢小乳蛋饼的便捷
I love the convenience of a nice mini quiche.
你那里有一点
You got a little, um...
不  好吧  好极了
Oh, no. Okay. Perfect.
新人还能再尴尬一点吗
Can the new guy embarrass himself any more?
大律师
Hey, counselor.
我要怎么做你才能把外套脱掉呢
What do I have to do to get you to drop that suit?
小卡  你怎么来了
Cam, what are you doing here?
给我的"抱抱老公"惊喜啊
Surprising my "Hugsband"!
这个词我还是第一次听说
I'm hearing that term for the first time.
是啊
Yeah.
你们什么时候回来
So when will you guys be back?
看来有人准备要取悦女同胞了
Looks like somebody's entertaining a lady friend.
也许你会给她斟一杯曼尼・施维滋美酒
Maybe you'll pour her a nice, tall glass of Manny-Schewitz?
你知道吗  有时候直接回答问题比较好
You know what? Sometimes just a straight answer.
歌洛莉亚  能给我个大概的时间吗
Gloria, can I get an E.T.A.?
这些都是重要的客户
These are important clients.
我希望我们到的时候他们还活着
I'd like them to still be alive when we get there.
好了  我准备好了
Okay! I'm ready.
真的吗
Seriously?
怎么了
What?
不  对不起
Ay, no! I'm so sorry!
我忘了是要和你的客户喝东西
I forgot this was drinks with your clients.
等等  好了
Hold on. Okay.
我准备好了  走吧
I'm ready now. Let's go.
你好呀  大明星
Hey, there, superstar.
白痴
Moron!
蠢货
Derp!
你不在的时候这里真是大不相同
It really hasn't been the same here without you.
你在看什么呢
So what do you got there?
大学宣传册
Oh, college brochure!
你要选学校了
You're gonna have your pick of schools.
你是我们的小天才
You're our little genius.
我只是希望
I just hope --
什么  克莱尔  你希望什么
What, Claire? What do you hope?
你的记录那么完美
Well, you have such a perfect record,
我希望他们不会给你不好的评价
I hope they don't hold it against you
因为你这周确实
that this week you kinda... well...
我不想用"半途而废"这个词
Don't want to say "Quit."
你已经用了
You just did.
你是想把我送回那个地狱吗
Are you trying to send me back to that hellhole?
不  宝贝  你是团队的一部分
No! It's -- honey, you're part of a team,
有人在指望着你呢
and there are people relying on you,
所以当你像这样消失时
so when you just up and vanish like that,
就好像
it sort of -- it --
菲尔
Phil?
Phil?!
你妈妈只是觉得这不像你
Your mom just feels like it's unlike you
你不是会撒手不管的人
to walk away from something.
至少我还能离开
At least I could walk away.
跟我住一个帐篷的人把脚钉在了地板上
My tent-mate nail-gunned her foot to the floor.
她就那样一边原地打转一边叫
She was just walking around in a circle screaming
直到有人发现了她
until someone found her!
为什么你们这么想赶我走
Why do you guys want to get rid of me so badly?
没人想赶你走
No one wants to get rid of you.
只不过是再呆七天
It's just seven more days.
善始善终会让你感觉很好的
You'll feel good about finishing something you started,
然后你就可以跟我们一起度过
and then you join us for the perfect little summer
这完美的夏天了
we're having here.
直到一小时前都很完美
Were having until an hour ago.
海莉
Haley!
天呐  好吧  我懂了
Oh, my god. Okay, I see what this is.
我不在你们都会高兴一点
You all are happier when I'm not here.
不  不是这样的
No, that's not true.
省省吧
Save it!
我会搭车回去的
I'll get a ride back up there
然后你们所有人就能继续
and you all can continue to enjoy
享受你们完美的小夏天了
your perfect, little summer!
-艾丽克斯  宝贝  -别理我
- Alex, honey! - Leave me alone!
电影台免费了
We just got free Cinemax!
这是米奇尔在亲一只海豚
Here's Mitchell kissing a dolphin.
这是他在亲一只老虎
Oh, that's him kissing a tiger.
我就是那只老虎
I'm the tiger.
我们太开心了
We have fun, you know?
我们可以带配偶来的吗
Were we supposed to bring our spouses?
小卡  小卡  听着
Hey, Cam? Cam, hey, look.
这活动只限员工参加
Um, this is kind of work-only.
拜托  他们都没发现我在这
Oh, please. They don't even know I'm here.
我喜欢这首歌  我们跳舞吧
I love this song. Let's dance.
不  不  没有人跳舞
No, no. Nobody's -- nobody's dancing.
用屁股来交流吧
Shh. Say it with your hips.
好吧
O-kay.
别这样  小卡
Hey, uh, no, Cam. Um...
你知道我爱你  对吧
You know I love you, right?
第一个用正确的方式爱我的人
First man that ever did love me right!
我们很开心
We have fun.
确实是  我们是的
We do, we do, we do.
所以  我在想  也许
Um, so, look, I-I was thinking that maybe...
我们可以把浪漫行为减少一点
we could turn the romance down
就一点点
just a little bit, you know?
因为这些事变得有点
Because it's been getting a little bit --
我不想说是过分了  但是
I-I-I don't want to say over the top, but it --
好吧  如果你想继续跳舞的话
Okay, I'm gonna need your help
我需要你也动起来
if we're gonna keep dancing here.
我感觉到你生气了
I feel like you're mad.
我们搞了个非正式的投票
So, we had an informal vote over there...
我们没有在跳舞了
We're not dancing anymore.
那就好
Oh, good.
你知道赫布可能会来的  对吧
You know Herb might stop by, right?
他给公司新闻简报拍照配图
He takes the pictures for the company newsletter.
知道  我很喜欢看《赫布宣传报》
Yes, I love "Herb's blurbs."
好了
Well...
到大门了
Here come the doors!
一般高档的地方都会有的
Usually all the good places have them!
我要开门了哦
I'm going to open them!
你真是个绅士  杰
Oh, you're such a gentleman, Jay.
我好像没带钱包
I think I forgot my wallet.
别担心
Oh, don't worry.
我腰包里有钱
I have some money here in my fanny pack, huh?
看在上帝的份上  好吧  你赢了
For god's sake, fine. You win.
我喜欢你打扮漂亮的样子
I like it when you make yourself pretty.
我赢了
I win!
我刚说过你赢了
I just said you won.
杰  我发现你不再为我打扮时
Ay, Jay, what you're feeling right now
跟你现在的心情是一样的
is what I feel when you stop trying to look good for me.
我知道的
No, I get it.
那你为什么不打扮了
Then why did you stop trying?
因为
Because...
算了吧  理由太蠢了
Oh, forget it. It's too stupid.
告诉我
Tell me.
几个月以前
A couple of months ago,
我在巴尼百货店买衣服
I was shopping at Barneys --
你知道我喜欢赶时髦
you know I like to stay current.
当我走出更衣室的时候
Anyhow, I'm coming out of the dressing room,
我看到两个年轻人在笑我
and I see these two young guys laughing at me,
像是在说"一把年纪了还赶时髦"
you know, like "There's the old guy trying too hard."
我当然很生气了
You know, of course I get mad.
可我却开始觉得
But I start thinking,
他们说得没错  杰
"They're right, Jay.
你老了  就别装嫩了
You're old. Just be old."
听着  杰・普里契特
Listen to me, Jay Pritchett!
很多人以为
A lot of people assume
我嫁给你是为了钱
that I married you because of your money,
这只是其中非常非常小的一部分
and that's only a very, very small part of it.
这点我们需要再聊一下
I'd like to go back to that.
我嫁给你是因为你很性感
I married you because you were sexy.
现在依然如此
You still are.
谁知道能保持多久呢
Who knows for how long that's gonna last,
我们俩都一样
for either of us.
所以我们都要为对方努力
So we have to keep making an effort for each other.
下次去巴尼百货  我陪你去
Next time you go to Barneys, I go with you.
说不定你只是选错衣服了
Maybe you're just making the wrong choices.
至少选你选对了
Not always.
你想喝点东西吗  我可以换件衣服
You want to have a drink? I can change.
不  我还是发短信跟他们说我病了吧
No, I think I'll text them, tell them I was sick.
我们回家吧  你刚说我很性感
Let's go home. You said I was sexy.
好了  再见  罗莎  谢啦
Okay, bye, Rosa. Thank you.
小卡
Cam!
怎么了  哥们儿
What's up, dude?
你叫我什么
Seriously?
怎么  你觉得这个也太浪漫了吗
What, is that too romantic for you?
他不爱我
He loves me not...
He loves me not.
我们能聊聊吗
Okay, can we talk?
不行  我有点忙
Actually, no. I'm kind of busy.
你大概忘了今天是我们结婚三周月
I'm assuming you forgot it's our three month-iversary.
我傻不拉几地布置了一番
Well, I foolishly set up a celebration
不过放心  我会清理掉的
that I will kindly get rid of.
小卡
Cam!
不  我没忘
No, I didn't forget,
但我想跟你说的就是这个
but that's what I want to talk to you about.
你有点太
You've been a little bit --
瞧  这就是我要说的
See, look. This is what I'm talking about.
你又给了我一个礼物
You got me another present.
别碰它
Don't touch that.
我的心啊
Oh, my -- my heart!
你哪有心啊
What heart?
小卡  不是吧
Cam! Come on!
好吧  听着
Okay, listen.
我知道能和你在一起我是多么幸运
I know how lucky I am to have you,
但是我承受不了你这么高强度的感情
but I can't possibly keep up with this level of affection...
天呐
Oh, boy.
我道歉  我是个禽兽
I apologize! I'm a monster!
不  很明显我才是禽兽
No, obviously, I'm the monster.
很明显
Obviously.
我能指出
You know, can I just point out
我们在卡波圣卢卡斯的时候
that when we were in Cabo,
你没有介意那些花啊
you didn't seem to mind all the flowers...
是的  可是
Yeah, but --
或是背部按摩
or the back rubs,
或是我对你的感情
or the attention.
那  那是我们的蜜月啊
Well, that -- that was our honeymoon,
没错  我很喜欢  可都过了好几周了
And, yes, I loved it, but it was weeks ago.
也许我们中有人不希望那种感觉结束
Well, maybe some of us don't want it to... end!
可是最终还是要结束的啊
Well, it has to eventually end.
好吧  小卡
All right, Cam --
这口红是你的吗
Did you have this lipstick or --
要知道  我觉得
You know, personally,
我很遗憾你这么保守
I feel sorry for you that you're so shut off
连一点浪漫的举动都
that a few simple romantic gestures --
天呐  我看的这是什么
oh,my god! What am I looking at here?
我想是我太疯狂
Well, I guess I'm crazy,
自从我们结婚以后
because I've taken pictures of you sleeping
我每晚都会拍你睡着的样子
every night since we got married
因为你是我的梦中情人
because you're the man of my dreams.
问个问题  如果我是你的梦中情人
Okay, super quick -- if I was the man of your dreams,
睡着的那个人不应该是你吗
wouldn't you have to be the one sleeping?
不要再说了[拉那条线]  米奇尔
Don't pull that thread, Mitchell.
我正好想问  这条线是什么
Speaking of which, what is this?
不要拉那条线  米奇尔
Don't pull that thread, Mitchell.
小卡  拜托
Oh, Cam, come on!
连你也得承认这有点过分了吧
Even you have to admit this is excessive.
过分  你真这么觉得
Excessive? Really?
你被丘比特的神箭射中了
Struck by Cupid's magic arrow.
结束了  莉莉
It's off, Lily.
不是吧  跟罗莎排练了两个小时呢
Seriously? Two hours rehearsing with Rosa?
小卡  你到底怎么了
Cam, what is going on with you?
我们刚刚经历了最浪漫的一年
We just had the most romantic year ever,
策划了我们的纪念日  婚礼还有蜜月
planning our ceremony, the wedding, the honeymoon,
我担心一旦松懈下来
and I'm just worried if we let this go,
我们就再也浪漫不起来了
we'll never get it back.
这些又不会就这么结束了
Well, that doesn't all just end.
已经发生过一次了
It did once.
我们刚住在一起的前两年
You know, the first two years we were together,
我们是那么的浪漫
we were insanely romantic.
然而后来就只剩孩子和工作了
Then it became about parenting a-and working.
直到过去这年我们又重新找回了浪漫
And this last year, we got that back,
我才发现是我没有坚持努力经营浪漫
and I just realized I've dropped the ball.
不
Oh, no.
也许不应该由你一个人
Well, m-maybe you -- you shouldn't be the only one
负责经营浪漫
carrying the ball.
要是你把这个责任递给我呢
What if you did a give-off to me?
是交给你
A hand-off.
好把  那
Okay, what -- yeah.
那要不我
Look, w-what if I...
试着变得浪漫些
tried to become a little bit more romantic?
那会是什么样呢
What would that even look like?
听这歌  听这歌
This song... this song...
是我向你提出同居那晚放的歌
Was playing the night I asked you to move in.
在苹果蜜餐厅
At that Applebee's.
你还欠我一支舞呢
I believe you owe me a dance.
是的
Yes.
这戏演完了没
Are we almost done with fairy time?
-莉莉别这样  -莉莉  这很没礼貌
- Lily, of all... - Lily, that's offensive.
我只是想换掉这身衣服
I just want to get out of this costume.
这样啊  当然可以了
Oh. Oh, of course.
这衣服看着确实不舒服
Now, that does look uncomfortable.
可以直接扯下来
They snap off.
扯下来就好  小意思
They snap off. Oh, that's easy.
马上就有人来接我了
My ride's on its way.
别担心  我会在屋外等
Don't worry, I'll wait outside on the curb.
宝贝  没人赶你走
Honey, nobody wants you to go.
哪怕你真的是灾星  也是我们的灾星
Yeah, even if you are bad luck, you're our bad luck.
你这话算哪门子道歉
You realize that is in no way an apology, right?
关键是  我们真的
The thing is that we are really --
别说了
Please stop talking.
我这个夏天到哪儿都是外人
I spent this entire summer as an outsider.
就连建房子  他们也是让我修外墙
They literally made me build the outside of the house.
就连回到自己家  都还...
And then I come back here and I --
你怎么开着摄像头
Why is your webcam on?
你是要偷拍我吗
Are you trying to humiliate me?
亮灯表示开着吗
That light means it's on?
我关掉网页时
It doesn't automatically turn off
摄像头不会自动关掉吗
when you go to a different web page?
不会  想想你把电脑放在床上
No, and considering you keep your laptop on your bed,
看得到你换衣服
right by where you change,
看得到你洗澡出来
and when you come out of the shower,
谁知道还能看到啥
and who knows what else...
大家都知道能看到啥
Everyone knows what else!
难怪你有五万个订阅者
It's probably why you have 50,000 subscribers.
你们真应该感到羞愧
Hey! You should be ashamed of yourselves!
好啦  好啦  还开着的
Yeah, yeah. Still not off.
你怎么关的
How do you do that?
慢着  有股味道
Wait, what is that smell?
你爸和卢克在做大黄派
Your father and luke are making a rhubarb pie
用的我们自家种的大黄
from rhubarb we grew in our own garden.
你走之前一定要尝尝
You're not leaving until you try it.
不不不  是烟味
No, no, no, no, no. I smell smoke.
我还没开烤炉呢
Well, I didn't turn the oven on yet.
你开了吗
Did you?
还没
No.
完了  完了
Oh, no, no!
我昨晚泡澡时打算看《战争与和平》的
I tried to start that stupid "War and Peace" again
结果在浴缸里睡着了
last night in the bathtub, but then I fell asleep.
书掉进了水里
It dropped in the water
我想着把它烘干
and I thought I would just dry it out.
快躲开
Take cover!
-好  好  -快躲开
- Okay! Okay! - Take cover!
天哪
Oh, god!
破烂玩意儿
Damn this thing!
没人看见烤炉亮着灯吗
Did nobody notice the oven light?!
同志们  指示灯是有意义的
Lights mean things, people!
漂亮
Great job!
天哪  完了  完了
Oh, god! Oh, no! No! No!
干得漂亮  宝贝
Good job, honey!
玩得真爽  但我的车到了
This has been awesome, but my ride's here.
祝你们玩得开心
Have a magical day.
别走  别走
No, no, no, no.
-别走  让我说  -别走  宝贝
- No, I got it. - No, sweetie.
-克莱尔  让我说  -好
- Claire, I got this. - Okay.
各位  吃一口
Spoon time, people.
好  我们家的传统
Yes! Family tradition.
好
Yes.
听着  宝贝  你想走可以走
Look, you can leave if you want to, sweetheart,
但我们得让你高高兴兴地走
but we're not letting you go without a smile on your face.
这里面满满都是我和卢克的爱
Luke and I poured a lot of love into this pie,
来
so, here...
尝一口
Taste this.
尝尝我们的爱
Taste our love.
你们把大黄的叶子去掉了吧
You took the leaves off the rhubarb, right?
叶子可是有毒的  会毒死你们的
They're incredibly poisonous. You all could die.
别吃  艾丽克斯说它有毒
No! Alex says they're poison!
我们也听见了
We're right here! We heard her!
你不能离开我们
You can't leave us.
不然我们会害死自己的
We're a danger to ourselves.
我们这家子有玩火的
We're a family of fire starters,
有吃毒药的  还有上网卖淫的
poison eaters, and online prostitutes.
这不是个完美的夏天
It wasn't a perfect summer.
是个愚蠢的夏天
It was a stupid summer.
没有你在旁边取笑我
Without you here to shame me,
我已堕落到看完全部《贵妇的真实生活》
I watched every "Real Housewives" episode
正经书却才看了两页
and I only got to page two in "War and Peace."
求你别走
Please stay.
我们家至少需要一个大人
We need at least one adult in this household.
好吧
Okay, fine.
你们知道天窗没关吧
You know the attic window is open, right?
还真不知道
We really didn't.
我们看谁先爬上楼
I race you up the stairs.
先去换件漂亮衣服吧
Why don't you slip into something less comfortable?
好
Okay!
惊喜哦
Surprise! Surprise! Surprise! Surprise!
我觉得  我们以后是不是别玩惊吓了
Just a thought -- maybe we should stop doing these.
你们搞什么
What's going on?
这还看不出来吗
It seems pretty obvious.
我故意把派对提前了一星期
I had to throw the party a week early
好真的给她一个惊喜
to really surprise her.
我们该担心吗
Should we be concerned about her?
当年老妈就是这么一走了之的
That's kind of similar to the way mom left.
歌洛莉亚和我在穿着打扮上闹别扭
Gloria and I got in this whole thing about how we dress.
说来话长
Long story,
我估计她要花点时间打扮一下
I think she might need a little more time bef--
大家好
Hola!
我里面穿着这身衣服呢
I had this outfit underneath.
你不会真以为
Did you really think
我会穿成那样进酒吧吧
that I was gonna walk into a bar looking like that?
谢谢
Gracias!
这些年害我好苦啊
All these years,
原来你瞬间就能打扮好啊
You're telling me you can get ready that fast?
[海莉的博客  订阅: 13976人]
[海莉的博客  订阅: 20267人]
加勒比女王
Caribbean queen
我们分享着...
Now we're sharing the --
天哪真好吃
Oh, my god!